Hello.
Morning, James. What's going on?
What's happening? How you doing, man? I'm doing great.
Good to meet you. Doing Hey, good to meet you.
Good to meet you. I love, I love the accent, bro.
I'm sorry. I'm jealous a little bit. What
Accent are you talking about?
You are the one with the accent for me. I've got
The accent. I know, right?
Um,
you're in South Africa, right?
Yeah, that's correct. Yeah.
So like, there's a, there's a few movies that are like,
based outta South Africa and like, I'm obsessed with them.
Um, like Chappy District, district nine.
Um, okay. Have you, have you seen them?
Yeah. Yeah, I have. Yeah, I have.
That's, uh, amazing. Um, yeah, anyways, I watched 'em
with my kids, like recently,
even though I probably shouldn't have shown them.
Um, and it's just like, it's a very unique,
very unique, uh, accent.
But, uh, glad you're here. Um, ca Is it Ca or Cal?
Callie. Callie.
I, I, I'm not sure how to pronounce your name, brother.
I don't wanna mess it up, even
though I probably already did.
Yeah, it's Callie.
Callie. All right. Yes. What's going on? Callie?
Good to, good to hear your voice. Glad to have you here.
Yeah, you too. You too. Amazing. I see, uh, Jana's in here.
Say hello if you can,
um, we got Ethan.
What's cracking Ethan?
Sparse. Just joined. What's up brother?
What's up John? How's it going, man?
It's going great. Um,
Yo, what's up Spars?
Good to meet you, bro. What's
Up James? How's it going?
Only chat. Jonas
Says good man.
Doing great. How are, how are you doing?
I'm doing great. Yes, sir. Good. That's
Good. Yeah. I want
to ask about your hat.
'cause you have a Bass Pro shop hat, um, so I don't know.
I love Do they have that in, in South Africa?
No, they don't. No, they don't. Okay.
It's, it's not a thing at all.
Um, we've, we've got other, we've got other brands
that are like similar, uh, meaning if you were
to see this in, in our country,
but it's not our Mark old business part.
And, and best friend, um,
we started our first business together when we were in
school, when we were 17.
And he, him
and his family moved to Canada about two years ago.
Um, and they came down last month and visited four month.
And, and this was one of the, one of the gifts that they,
they came back and gave me was a fast pro cap.
Um, as if it's not touristy enough.
I love it. Well, they're actually opening one up kind of
by my house, and there hasn't been a location like,
very far from each other.
So there's a joke
because I, I really like to go like fishing.
Like that's something I do on my off time.
And, uh, same, my wife, she's like, dude,
you need to go get a job there.
She's like, you need to go work there
so you can get discounts.
I'm like, I'm like, yeah, that would be a great idea.
Me just, you know, working there while on my phone on Slack,
like, Hey guys, sorry, I gotta go take this, uh, customer.
Um, but yeah.
We'll, we'll give a couple more minutes,
a few more people are joining in.
Um, but I am, I'm really excited
and I'm, I'm, I'm grateful you're able, you're able
to jump on and share some things, share some insights,
and I would love for everyone to just collaborate in this,
um, q and a session that we're gonna be doing.
I know a few people here, uh,
but I definitely see some new faces, so it's nice to see
new faces here in the lives.
And, um, and yeah, we'll just give it a couple more minutes,
but, um, what's everyone's time zone?
Wherever you guys are at in the world right now?
Drop it into the chat.
19:00 PM Damn. Is that like 10?
That's seven. Seven, yeah. 7:00 PM Got it.
Yeah. People are, people do that 24 hours.
Um, that's not too bad.
I hope that's not crazy for you guys.
Oh, 11:00 PM that's, you're like,
Yeah, it's the same for me.
Yeah, you're like, it's sparse land, multipliers, media.
I think he's in, are you in Pakistan? Um, got
Pakistan. Might be somewhere in
South Asia,
maybe Thailand or somewhere, I
Think. Love it.
Drop your countries in the, in the, in the chat.
Love to, I know we got Pakistan south, um, South Africa.
I know Jana Jana's from Germany. Think. Yes.
England. There it is. Sweden. Sweden living in Italy.
Dude, that just sounds like a dream.
I I haven't been to any of those places.
I would love to one day.
Um, maybe we'll, uh, we'll do some sort of world tour and,
and come, come together one day, but, uh,
but I would love to just get started.
I don't wanna take up anyone's time,
but I would, uh, James, you cool with that?
Yeah, let's run it. All right. I'm done. Cool. Amazing guys.
Well, we'll keep it, keep it small today.
And, um, for anyone who's unable to join,
we'll post the recording.
Um, today I want to introduce James.
He's a, a new member to Ads Orx.
And I, when I saw his introduction, I just kind
of felt a really good energy coming from him
and seeing that he had worked with a lot
of seven figure brands, um, and checking out his LinkedIn
and seeing kind of a history of his creative journey.
Everyone has a different one. Um, I wanted to bring him on
because I just felt like, uh, a good op.
I, I know a lot of people in the community have
so much value to offer,
and this is something that I wanna continue doing, uh,
throughout the year, is just bringing people on from
different, um, expertise levels
and sharing what you guys know,
because, you know,
I've seen some pretty impressive people in the community
and I would love to have them on.
So, James, you know, congratulations for being one
of the first, uh, new members, uh,
to be on a call this year.
James, if you don't mind just kind of giving your,
your intro to everybody, a little bit
of background about yourself and what to, what,
what people can expect from you today.
Yeah, for sure. Um, how far back do I go? Do I go like,
When you were born, you know,
like the first day Okay, you came out the hospital.
Yeah, so my mom and my dad, um, once they, I'm kidding.
So, um, I, I would say I, I, I always like
to tell people my, my first business I ever started was,
was called Misfit Media.
Um, and, and my best friend
and I always felt like we're misfits.
Um, and so, you know, where, whether that, whether
that be we were, you know, rebellions in school, we,
we just kind of went against the system
with everything we did, whether it was something we chose
to do, just naturally, that's what happened.
Um, that, that's just how we found ourselves.
We, we found, we, we only really got on with
like, our friends' parents.
Like that's where the people we connected with.
We couldn't connect with people our age.
We, um, and,
and we, we just, you know, in school,
we're against the school system against this educational
system, you know, how,
how can we be learning such traditional methods of,
of something when there's a modern day society out there
that requires different means of doing things.
So, long story short, we started out in business
and it was pretty much a, we did photography, videography
and, and some social media for local businesses.
And, and that's kind of what, what got us started.
And I think that that taste of entrepreneurship is something
that I'll never be able to let go of.
Um, and it's, it's waking up every day with the desire
to just find more clients, find new business,
um, whatever it may be.
And for us, at the time, it was, you know, photography,
videography where we would pack our camera bags.
We would go out in my car
and we would drive to
we'd every day we would choose a different niche.
So one day we would go, let, let's go to all the, the BMBs
and hotels in our area.
And we'd literally go ding-dong Dash, we'd,
we'd go knock on their doors
and we would say, hi there, we photographers,
videographer, we'd love to meet with the owner.
We'd love to offer you a free shoot.
If you love the photos, there'll be a small fee.
If you don't know hard
feelings, you never have to see us again.
And we did that day
after day at restaurants for events, for, you know,
entire places, car shops, we just, every niche.
Um, and, and that kind of just sparked this like, desire
of, of business within me.
And we, we, we naturally grew the business like that.
And, uh, it got to a point where, um, we made a good name
for ourselves in our local area
as these youngsters that were hustling.
Um, and eventually grew into the more social media side
of things where we found, hey, we could actually use our
laptop and sit at home and we can do work
and get paid instead of being out on the road grinding,
you know, all the physical hard labor of it.
Um, and, and so once we got a little taste
that social media, um, was where we started realizing
what else you can do online, um, when it comes
to running ads, when it comes to just, you know,
getting Google reviews for your local businesses
or whatever it may be.
Um, and we eventually stumbled into meeting an overseas
company at the time they were called hashtag our Stories,
um, founded by a guy named Yusuf Omar.
And they are pretty much an online social media news agency.
And they, they pretty much bought us out,
which was sounds great,
but it was the worst thing we ever did.
Um, because we were signed into a 12 month contract working
for them during that process.
And then we really fell into, um,
what it was like being an employee, working for someone,
working an nine to five, waking up, not choosing
what you get to do, and pretty much getting, doing
what you get told to do every day.
Um, and going from how we were
before into that really suppressed us, um,
and made us rebel, uh, a lot of things.
But yeah, it's, um, then Covid hit
and we were released from this 12 month contract.
Um, and now we were like, our roots of what we know works.
Photography, videography can't happen.
We can't go, we can't go out.
It's into the real world and do it.
We can't leave our houses, we're in complete lockdown.
Um, and so the, the forcing it out was we are not
to video edit, we're not to be creative.
We're not how to do social media.
Let's go ahead and do that. And naturally, uh, my,
my best friend and I partner and I split up
and we went separate ways, but, uh,
I eventually started working with some digital marketing
agencies, um, as a video editor.
And I was editing video ads
All day day,
Not that long, about about 18 months
of pure video editing all day every day for ads.
And it was a good shift for me.
Lemme know if I'm cutting out my wifi today has
been absolutely terrible.
You did cut out for a little bit there.
Um, I think I lost you with your, your editing video ads.
18 months every single day.
Yeah. So was was living and breathing, uh, video ads.
Um, and,
and over that time, I, I did gain, which, which is where I,
I see, um, is one of the key factors taking
that next level from a video editor into more
of a creative strategist role, is working closer
with the media buyers, understanding the data of
what you are producing
and understanding what you need to do with it.
Um, is that first kind of step to, to figuring it out.
And so, yeah.
Um, in, in that time of working
with a few different digital marketing agencies
and working with, um, quite a few different brands, um,
is every time I, I'd create something, I'd follow up
with a media by and say, you know,
Hey, how did that perform?
You know, can you share your screen?
Show me the ad account, you know, show me what happened.
Um, and then just from the advice
and conversations that I had with these media buyers,
I started figuring out how they think when,
when they're running ads.
Um, so I actually got to understand the media buying
processes a lot, as well as I got
to understand from a creative person perspective going,
okay, he's telling me all of this data,
but like, creatively, like,
what can you actually do with that?
What are you meant to do with it?
Um, because oftentimes it's,
if there's no creative strategists in the team,
the video editors are being briefed by media buyers.
And media buyers, as we know, aren't creative people.
They numbers people.
Although some media buyers I've met, I think have potential
to be the best creative strategist in the world.
But for most brands that,
that media buyers on accounts, they're numbers people.
So they're writing creative briefs for video editors
and not giving you much room to work with.
Um, and so I was always just kind
of pushing those boundaries
and saying, Hey, I know you sent through the brief
and it says this, but hey, what if, what if we,
we tried this, or Hey,
I could actually film something at my place quick.
That could be a crazy good hook, you know, and, and,
and just that, those type of things.
And, uh, um, eventually, uh, I I came across, uh, another
digital marketing brand working
with e-commerce brands here in South Africa,
but had, uh, international clients.
And they offered me more
of a creative strategist role based off of just, you know,
where, where I was at that stage
after, you know, being in the ground with video editing.
And then that's where I got to learn more
of the static side of things.
Um, not just video ads, but,
but also looking at static graphics and,
and their performance and,
and how things can change from there.
Um, and I was also doing video
editing, you know, jobs on the side, um, for four brands
for other e-comm agencies.
Um, and I then went from that agency
to another agency as a creative director,
where they wanted me to manage their creative strategists
as well as their video editors.
Um, and did that
for about six months.
Um, and, and from the, that's where I actually gotta see the
beauty that can happen with e-commerce brands
and the magnitude of sizes of e-commerce brands
that they're on in the world where there's a brand
that you have never heard of, you never knew exists,
but is making more money than you can imagine.
Um, and, and making it in, in such easy, what seems
to be an easy way.
And from there, I got, I gotta work
with creative strategists, like-minded people.
Started to connect with a lot
of people in the e-commerce space.
Um, that's where I found myself jumping into foreplay.
Um, got myself as, um, one of the experts on foreplay.
I know you, there's Experts tab.
Um, you go check me out to have a look at some of my boards.
My boards are very simple. I love it.
Um, I broke them down into UGC high production and static
'cause that's, that's all, all I think is necessary.
But yeah, you can go check me out on foreplay.
Um, but yeah, and, and,
and just go to connect with some really cool people in the
space, um, and get a lot of insights, whether it just be
through conversations as
what other brands are doing creatively, um, and,
and what ad creative can look like in the e-commerce space.
And, and in very detailed manner, um, when it comes
to every aspect of it.
Um, as, as your course as, as this course goes through, um,
starting at the very beginning, you know,
researching the product, researching the brand,
the pain points, the desires, leaning into the emotion
as the foundation to build off of the ad creative.
Um, and all the way through to, you know,
once you see performance
and you see data, what does the data mean?
And, and how can you make changes iterate, um,
and, and improve from there.
Um, and then, uh, this, uh, last year, um, Jan,
I started working with Flex Labs.
This is the agency I'm currently with, um,
where I'm the creative team, lead,
creative director, whatever you wanna call me.
And I work with the creative team, um, as part
of the creative service
that we offer with the e-commerce brands.
We work with, currently, we work
with about 30 active clients, or e-commerce brands, um, and,
and all different niches,
all different places around the world.
And they are very well established brands.
Um, and yeah, that's
where I find myself now working at the Flex Labs team,
working with my creative team.
Um, and yeah, just loving every second of,
of going deep and deep into add creative.
Wow. Thank you, man. That was impressive story.
Very, very relatable.
Um, drop in the comments, like
what you guys thought of that story?
Was it relatable? Have you guys have
a, do you have a similar story?
Um, I know there's different, different types
of people here right now in the group,
at least the current group, but then
different people in the community.
But I know, um,
after speaking with Jana, actually, uh, the other day,
she has an agency as well,
and she's trying to integrate new systems, creative systems,
and, uh, integrating creative as a service,
um, into her agency.
So maybe she might, you, you might wanna think about
how we can help Jana's today's
Call. That's exactly what I've just built
for Flex Lab,
so whatever you wanna ask. Shoot. Um,
There you go. Yeah.
Um, I know Callie, he's, you're an editor, right?
Maybe creative strategist.
Um, we have Ethan, who's a, uh, age, uh,
video ad agency, uh, owner.
So he has a team of editors
and he's like slowly getting to the creative strategy,
uh, place right now.
Um, Aaron, I'm not sure where you at, um, in terms of like,
if you're an agency owner or a a, an editor,
but share anything that you, you wanna,
you wanna discuss today.
Um, and we have Multipliers Media.
I'm not sure what your first name is, brother,
but I know you're, uh, you're like media buyer slash editor.
Is is that, but there's a, there's a big group,
there's a mixed bag, right?
So, um, I wanted to see where we can
potentially just drop some value or some hints
or clues as to like, what's the next step, right?
Because everybody wants to level up in their own way, right?
So depending on where you're at in your business
or in your company, like,
what's the next stage and how do we get you there?
'cause it sounds like you've, you've walked through all
of those steps, right?
And, uh, oh, sick dude, agency,
co-owner and creative director.
Let's go. Agency owner. We do creatives for D F**k. Yeah.
Excuse my language. Um, amazing.
So we're all speaking the same language here.
Um, so yeah, I think what,
what have been some of the, the challenges, um,
you've experienced just overall working with editors
and media buyers
and just like, where are things disjointed?
I, I must say, I think, and,
and I don't think there ever is a solution for it.
'cause I think it's always about adapting to it.
But I, I see a, a great disconnect with
testing cadences and a volume of creative.
You know, there's, there's some brands that I speak with
or some agencies I'm with where they're like, dude,
you gotta be testing 10 pieces
of creative every single day nonstop.
Like, and then there's, you know, um, and,
and then I've seen huge success with brands
where we do one creative batch a week.
And, um, and the counts is absolutely crushing it.
And it's figuring out where's a sweet spot.
Um, you know, what is the balance between video creative,
static creative, um, obviously you can run lots
of different ads, um, even outside of static
and video, um, as well.
So it's, it's, um, challenges that I've found is, is trying
to find this kind of sweet spot for brands,
because every brand is different as well.
You know, you can, I, I looked at some data yesterday, um,
when I was reviewing some accounts,
and it's one brand
statics just do, do not work.
We test it all the time.
Video creative carries this account
and there's nothing that can outperform video creative.
But then ano,
there's one other account while I was reviewing the same
time, videos don't work at all,
but then there's some statics that are crushing it.
Mm-Hmm. Um, and it's like, the difficult part is,
is you gotta make your decisions based off the data
and remove your motion as the creative person, which is,
in the beginning, I found the most difficult thing was,
is having a media buyer come back to me and tell me a video.
I spent 12 hours editing. Oh, it didn't work. Mm-Hmm.
And I was like, show me.
And he is like, oh, we spent $200 and it didn't work.
I'm like, dude, you can't tell me after that.
It, it doesn't work. You know?
Um, and then my motion gets involved.
Whereas you gotta look at the data
and the data, if it's telling you video games
or anything is working, do you fully just go into that 100%
and don't even think and look back at static?
Or does that mean that hey, there's actually room to
find the winning statics
and find, you know, the formats outside of
what is already working.
Obviously you, you will make iterations
and build on what you know is working.
But, um, yeah, just navigating through that.
'cause every single counts is different and seasons change
and advertising changes, meta is constantly changing.
Meta's algorithm is changing.
Um, it's, you know, the strategy is always changing.
Yeah. And so you have the foundations that will never leave.
You know, you, there's the foundations of advertising,
which you can go and read breakthrough advertising,
but Edward Ogilvy, that will never change.
That's human psychology in advertising.
But there's the more deeper aspects
of it when it actually comes to the tangible formats,
the ads, um, where things, things do change.
So I would say that's, it's a challenge that I'm,
I'm constantly trying to adapt to and, and, and figure out.
Absolutely. Yeah. I, like I said, I agree.
It's, it's, every account is different,
every message is different, every audience is different,
you know, and, um, as much as we wanna generalize, you know,
like the same thing for every single brand.
Yeah. It's like everyone's saying something different.
And I've realized after working with hundreds of brands,
like everyone's doing something different.
Like no one has fully figured it out,
like in their business.
Yeah. I don't care if you're a hundred million dollar
company, and I've, I've talked
to a hundred million dollar companies,
they're like, yeah, we st I don't know.
We just do it like nobody. Like, there's no perfect way.
You, you are figuring it out, right. Um, as you go.
And that's where I feel like, um,
yeah, and it's, it's like just sharing your wins along the
way and seeing if people can apply that
to their businesses, right?
Because it's like, this, this worked for me,
but it may not work for you.
And what worked for you may may work for me.
So I think that's what a community's all about.
Um, let's talk about, um,
maybe systems.
I know Jana's really into systems.
Are you, are you involved in that process at all?
Me or Jana? Uh, You,
Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
For sure,
For sure. So like,
um, let's talk about KPIs.
I think this is a really important one. Yeah.
Just overall, 'cause like bandwidth output, as we all know,
or most of us are here, are like editors
or some sort of editor.
Um, and, you know, editing takes a ton
of time, you know what I mean?
But like, the demand is so high,
and it's like, you want high quality
and you want it yesterday, right?
And so it's like, how do you balance that?
How do you balance like the demand plus the creative side
without like, burning out and making it predictable?
Yeah, that's a great question.
Um, I, I would say that
fortunately I've gone through the ranks
of being the video, the video editor.
Mm-Hmm. Um, and, and so I know how much time it takes,
and I know the issues you can come across as an editor.
You know that when you import iPhone footage
and the colors off, you know
that there's a few workarounds you gotta do, you know that
you can have export setting issues
and it's, it's gonna take you 10 minutes
to figure it out, whatever it is, you know?
Mm-Hmm. Um, there's always,
you always gonna come across these things
that may take longer setbacks.
Um, and, and tedious of editing.
I do feel like editing software has come a long way
since our first started editing.
Um, I remember editing documentaries
or half an hour documentaries
and typing out the subtitles letter by letter.
Wow. Yeah. Um, uh, like it's, uh, you know, so,
so editing softwares have come a long way,
but, um, so I think
because I've gone through that,
I don't set very high expectations on my editors.
Whereas I've worked with teams where the team leads
weren't editors and they're the media buyer,
or they, they account strategist
or the, uh, they're copywriter or,
or whatever it is, um, that don't, can't relate.
They do set unrealistic APRs.
They do have unrealistic expectations on the video editor
and the video editing team that, that yeah.
As you said, is just un unrealistic
and editing ads all day every day,
you're not going to get the high quality of ads
every single time you edit that.
That's, that's just what's gonna happen. Mm-Hmm.
Um, and so I've learned that with my team setting
realistic APRs, where it actually allows the team
to not feel rushed, not feel under strict deadlines,
allows a better quality of work to be produced,
which just leads to better results for clients.
So I would rather get less of volume of creative out
of an editor, but higher quality where I know
that this is what's gonna carry the ad account forward
than testing a whole bunch of stuff, which we know
that we just throwing s**t at
the wall and hoping something sticks.
Um, and yeah.
Um, with regards to specific KPIs, KPIs
that I've, I've, I've played around
with a few different KPR measures.
One that I've found, um, working
to be quite well is having a 50% success rate.
So out of the video ad and,
and what we call a batches.
And so a batch would be one video
with five different hook variations.
You know, that's a batch 'cause it's one main edit,
just different variations of it.
And each batch we look back
and, uh, in a two week reviewing, okay,
the last two weeks we made 10 batches, five
of the 10 50% should in the ad account, be
above the ad account media buying KPIs, which is, you know,
that it's, the return is profitable, you know,
at a certain level, whether we are aiming for a target CPA,
uh, you know, cost per acquisition,
or maybe we're wanting to lower CPCs, whatever the, the
KP is for the media buying team.
If our creative that we are making, is
that a 50% success rate to that, then that's, that's a KPI
that, that we have set.
Um, but you know, we've, we've tried KPIs
where it's about volume and not about success of it.
So like the KPIs are just to make two batches a day
every workday or, you know, um, having numbers to number
of videos that need to be produced.
But I think it's better to have a success rate where it's
allows the video to, to actually think more carefully
and spend more time in the actual creative
to make sure it's performing better.
Not just hitting volume numbers.
'cause then they're just hitting the numbers for the
numbers, not thinking about the quality of it.
Um, tho those are just some
of the KPI metrics I've played around with.
That's amazing. That's,
that's really valuable that you for sharing.
Um, and I, I, I totally agree.
I think it's, it's those batches, right?
It's like, um, one creative is like a style.
It's, it's a concept. And you wanna put that out.
I'm, I'm, I'm curious to know about,
and feel free anybody can join in on this
conversation, guys, for sure.
Okay. Kale has a question
regarding batches and perfecting them.
Can you expand on that question?
Yeah. Hey guys, I'm gonna turn on my camera
for this one. There
It is, dude. Love to be, bro.
Yeah, I, I wanted to know, like, regarding batches
and so maybe we created batch of ads
that are performing well.
Um, and we're kind of like split, uh, often.
Like, should we put more time perfecting that batch of ads?
Or should we like go on
and try to create another batch that performs,
like learn from that batch and create a new batch.
Maybe, you know, the making it better.
Um, but then again, we've done that
and we've seen that the next batch maybe performance worse.
So like, what's your view on that?
Yeah, I'm happy to take this, John, if you want,
You want me to take this?
Yeah, I think it's, oh,
Um, sorry, my, sorry.
My internet's glitching out. Oh, my bad.
Saying, I, I was like, you just froze. I was asking if you,
if if you're happy for me to take it,
but if you wanna take it, I'm done. I
Would love for you to take it. Yeah. And
I can add my little, what my thoughts on it too.
Okay, sweet. Yeah, I think it, I think it comes down,
first of all to understanding what's you're testing
in the batch so that when you do see performance, you know
what is working and what's not.
So we have iteration batches
and we have new concept batches.
So we treat batches as two separate iterations
and new concepts or new ideas, you know, new angles.
Um, and we always base
our creative off of a concept off one idea, not many.
So that if we know that one concept is working, we know
that we can make iterations on it
and we can actually make new creative in different
formats of the same concept.
Because at the end of the day, it's,
it's usually the messaging of the ad that's is leading
to the performance, not the format of it.
So it's not usually the, the quick cuts,
color grading sound effects that is
making someone click on the ad to go and make a purchase.
It's the messaging, it's the motion you're making them feel.
The editing adds to it 1000% super crucial.
But the actual messaging
and the core concept is the foundation of it.
So if we find that there's a winning batch
that is performing and,
and working well, we will create an iteration batch off
of it where we'd realize
and say, Hey, okay, we know that this hook is working
and the is
heading
the add a format.
Is there a creator that we are working with
that can hit a similar type of idea to go
and get them to shoot content?
Um, how can we elaborate
and bold off of a certain concept of idea
and then iterating off of it iterations?
You can make endless amounts of iterations endless.
Um, and like literally endless
because if you take the formula
of breaking down a video into blocks,
you can misconceive these blocks into unlimited amounts
of storylines as well as if you just take one
of the pieces of the story blocks out,
then you've got a shorter video ad
that you can miscon consume to lots of different storylines.
You can add blocks, you can change the blocks,
you can adjust the blocks.
Um, so iterations you is,
there's a lot you can build off of that.
But usually if you know the foundation of
what you're building off of, you know, what's working,
what's not, and then you can just iterate off of that.
Does that answer your question at all?
If it doesn't, like just say so
and I, I, I can dive into if, if I didn't. No,
No. It, it, it, it
really does.
Um, I guess the, the only question that remains for me, um,
perfect answer, great answer.
Thank you. Um, but my question is kind of like what, um,
like percentage wise,
how much time do you put into making iterations
on something that is working?
And how much time are you putting into like, creating,
trying to find other winning concepts?
You know, so for an example, work with,
with the skincare brand,
and we know that one concept, one angle is like, uh, it
actually like removes uh, your wrinkles
around your eyes, let's say, for example.
And we know that we can, we have tried
that in many different ways, static video
and different, like storylines, et cetera.
But like, how much time should we put on doing that?
And, and yeah, I, I guess,
Yeah. So
you, if you find a winning ad, make iterations,
obviously that ad the media buyer is gonna scale,
is gonna put more budget towards,
or Facebook will naturally do that.
But make iterations
and base your next decision off of that iteration.
So if you do make iterations off of that ad
and you don't see any performance, then take
that main idea and go
and build off of it in a different way.
But don't keep iterating.
Don't, if, if you find a winning ad
and you make a batch of iterations off of this winning ad,
so you find a winning, winning video
and you're gonna make another five iterations of this video,
if you don't find any performers in these five,
that doesn't mean you now need to take these five
and now go make another five.
Okay. You, you iterate based off of the learnings
that you can get directly from what you are seeing.
So if you do find that iterations you made,
you seen good performance in this, then
keep iterating off of the winners.
It's as simple as that.
And it, and it's a, it's a building block
and the more it's, um, it, it kind of, uh,
um, what's the word I'm looking for?
It, uh, exponentially grows
as you keep finding these iterations and, and winners.
But I, I always suggest that whether you are iterating
or not, you are always testing new ideas and new concepts.
So iterations are seen as bonuses.
You should always have a new concept
and new idea lined up that
you're working on, that you're gonna test.
Iterations are something that you should be available
and able to make any time unlimited amounts of.
If there are winners, and it's a bonus, it's a add-on,
it should be something that you don't plan for
and don't expect, but you're so ready for.
But new concepts
and new angles is so non-negotiable that you always need
to be testing and trying in an account.
And iterations are something that you only do once
you get the feedback and the data to make that decision.
But you should already be making decisions with
or without data on new ideas and new concepts.
Col, kale, um, I wanted to ask
for your skincare brand, and thank you for sharing.
That was amazing. Um, did you,
have you found a winning ad winning angle yet for that?
Um, yeah, and that's, uh, like I said, it was, it's um,
uh, you know, like the wrinkles around the eyes and,
and also we found that we have gotten a lot of organic,
like reviews on our website.
So like one angle that we use is like, don't trust me,
read the reviews on the website
and we like, send them there.
Mm-Hmm. And, uh, and they like read the reviews
and they're all organic
and very well, like, uh,
they post photos, et cetera, et cetera.
So that has worked very well, for example.
Amazing. And I would just add to, to that concept.
So it's like we found, we found the winning angle,
the winning messaging don't trust me, right?
So there's uh,
there's objection handling happening there, right?
So how do we iterate on that?
Because that's what's drawing people in.
Um, people are naturally skeptic, right?
So if people are skeptical,
how can we overcome their skepticism, uh,
in different formats, in different ways?
Um, so just like top of my mind, it's like,
I can't bel like, you know, then you start going into,
then you can channel your creativity into a box of, okay,
let's just think about negative angles, right?
Negative messaging. Um,
and then that becomes all these new winning concepts,
almost like proven because you, you have tested it
and that gives you ads for indefinite amount of time.
And then while you're doing that,
that's like your winning concept.
Then you can test, you know, 20% new concepts,
maybe new angles at the bottom there.
But it's, it's this tree map, right?
As like, as you expand it, it's like the winning concept.
Then now let's expand it into different formats,
different avatars, right?
Different demographics. 'cause
that's gonna resonate differently too.
Um, but yeah, I think, yeah, I mean we can keep going on
that, but does that answer your question?
Right, right, right, right. Uh, definitely. Thank you.
Thank both of you. I don't want
to like take, take up all this in.
I seen that Jan, uh,
Jana has written something here in the chat.
Maybe we could answer that question.
I think, I think just to add one last thing onto
that though is, um, and as John, not to repeat 'em,
but you, when you do find a winning ad, try
and find the pure emotional pain point as
to why that was the winning A
because if it's wrinkles around the Rs, that could be,
is it wrinkles around the Rs
because that is physically unhealthy?
Probably not. Is it because it makes people feel old
and aging, so then is the emotion insecurity
because they don't want other people seeing their
wrinkly and thinking they're old.
So then I would say then the, the, you could look at it
as the winning concept is not wrinkly
as the winning concept is insecurity or wrinkly as
because of insecurity.
'cause then you can build off of that.
You have a lot more of a foundation
and a lot more building blocks to build off of.
'cause then you can start really leaning into, okay,
customer demographic is probably 40, 30 plus females.
They got wrinkly eyes and they're super insecure.
Why would they be insecure? Maybe
their friends are gossiping.
Let's make a creative around, um,
my bestie told me I'm getting too old.
You know? Uh,
and it's kind of like that is the same angle.
It's the same as, you know, the wrinkly approach,
but you're just leaning into these insecurities in more
emotional, you know, type of type of ways.
I love that so much. Yes.
The emotional, the emotional aspect is always
the very first block.
It's the first concept that's, yeah.
And then we, then you build on top. I love that.
Thank you for adding that. Um, so
Jana, Jan has a few questions there.
Naming, what naming conventions do you use?
Do you track the success rate? How do you manage iterations?
Do you use IDs? I think
she may be talking about the account.
I,
Yeah, I mean, I,
I wouldn't suggest Argos are naming conventions simply
because at Flex Labs we have our own internal
reporting software.
And the naming conventions we use is purely based off
of the reporting dashboard.
Um, so our naming is just a bunch of digits like color code,
I mean the client code digits, um, variation numbers,
copy numbers, landing page numbers.
Um, it's, it's just a combination of numbers and letters.
Um, and it's purely just
because of our reporting dashboard is that's
where we look to see data.
So I wouldn't be able
to go too deep into naming conventions.
I mean, I could, it's just,
it's not gonna really mean anything.
Um, so I'm, I'm curious,
does anybody here use like dynamic creative testing
to test messaging in, in initial ad concepts
or, uh, you guys doing like individual ad sets
and then kind of like the older, older way
of just putting everything into independent ad sets?
We do both. Do both.
Yeah. We, we do both.
Both. Okay. Cool. Amazing man.
Um, anybody else have any questions for, for James? I'm,
Yeah, I've got a question.
All right. What's up Ethan?
Hi. How you doing? Um, would you say for some products
or companies, there's no saving them, no matter
how good the creative strategist
or ad creative is, say if the product's really bad
or the company isn't very good at producing landing pages,
I'll just like hear your opinion on that.
Thank you.
Damn, what a question.
Um, I'm gonna give you
the answer that I would tell anyone I work with
and anyone I would talk to, which is you guys.
And then there's the answer that I
have at the back of my mind.
Um, the answer is, creative strategy.
Can, you can find a winning product of a s**t product
with good creative strategy.
You can save a brand with creative strategy.
You can take a brand from nothing
to something with creative strategy.
Creative strategy, I think is the foundation
or is the driver for the success of,
of majority of e-commerce brands.
Um, but then the, the, the thing
that I said I had at the back of my mind is, is,
and this is where I'll let go of my ego a little bit.
I've worked with brands that no matter
what I tried to do, it didn't work.
And so the answer that I had the back of my mind is, is yes,
no matter what you do, it, it, it won't work.
But, but that's only
because we eventually stopped working
with the client 'cause we couldn't get the results.
So maybe if we kept on working with the client,
things would've turned around and maybe at
that point in summer, I wasn't the best creative strategist
that was needed for that brand.
Maybe I just couldn't wrap my head around correctly
around this product, around this, you know, maybe we had
to take a completely different approach than I was.
Um, so I have worked with some accounts
and some brands where no matter what I tried,
but there was always small wins,
but nothing that could, you know,
really exponentially help the brand.
Um, and so yeah, my, my answer is creative strategy can,
you can market a s**t product really well
with good creative, um, and you can,
but I obviously have my own experience where
sometimes it's not the case.
But I think that's just a matter of time
because if I was still working with him today, I would,
you know, I I'm never the one that gives up
as obviously the client that always stops working with us.
But, um, you know, matter of time.
Thank you. Great answer.
Ethan, do you wanna share the product? So,
No, is it, it is not in particular.
I was just, I was just curious
because what the belief I always had in my mind was
that if you're a really, really good marketer,
you can pretty much sell any product to, to most people.
I was just curious what, what you thought
of that with all your experience?
Yeah, no, that's a good question.
Yeah, it's all amount of time.
I mean, it's like you can, shell, you can sell s**t to,
to, you know, a 5-year-old kind of thing.
You know, like a, if like you're persuasive enough,
you know, there's a, there's an angle, there's a desire
that you can twist in some way, shape or form.
But ultimately I believe,
'cause I've, I've worked with hundreds of brands
and like every product I swear I've seen it all.
And, um, it, and I've seen the worst of the worst products
and I've, I've had to fake
so much stuff and it's so annoying.
And, um, and then the client is always
like, no, just make it work.
It does it. And I'm like, bro,
this thing broke when we're shooting it.
Like, this is a piece of crap.
And like, I can't believe that you are gonna go sell
that out in the world.
And, um, you know, we produce a great ad
and then people are like, oh my God, this is amazing.
Does it work? I'm like, no, it's garbage.
So I think eventually,
even if a marketer does crack the code,
the business will suffer because it won't have the reviews
and the reputation that a great brand
and a great product, great customer
service will have, right?
So I know there's tons of marketers that kind of like,
you know, they prey on that.
Like, it's like just, they just get it out
and they don't really care about the customer.
But that's always been something that's, that never sat,
sat well with me.
Um, you know, just, just make the sale
and screw the rest kind of thing.
But that's kind of where like, I,
I feel like there's imbalance.
Um, but anyways, that, that, that was awesome.
Uh, anybody else have any questions? That was like,
You're gold bro.
Yeah, go ahead. That thing that said, um,
and it's really a quick,
and it's something I heard, I don't remember where,
but someone said like, a marketer can get you to, uh,
get your first sale to a person,
but it's always, always gonna be the product
that makes the sec them by the second time.
So like, you can sell a product, you can sell a product
to anyone, any product to anyone,
but they won't come back if the brand is not there,
if the product is not what it's, uh, says it to.
So like, might might go well for, for one one year,
uh, if you have a drop shipping store, I mean that's,
that's like the core of every drop shipping store.
Almost like you, you buy ship products
and you like hype it up and people buy it
and then they hate you and you need to close the store,
Then they hate you.
Um, there's a really funny, I don't know if it,
it was a long time ago, but it was like buying things from
the, like, it was like a, it was like a reel
and it was like buying things from Facebook ads.
And then, um,
and then it says like three weeks later, it was like a,
a remote control car that like could go on water
and it was like, it was like a jet ski.
Like, and you see the ad
and you're like, oh, this is so cool.
And then you get it and he drives it into the
pool and it just sinks.
It's just like, it's exactly true.
That's, that's, yeah, that's good marketing,
but, you know, crappy product.
Um, so yeah, that's, that's, uh, I wanted
to ask Asim.
Asim is, uh, I've worked with him, he is an editor,
but he's, he's a student right now
and he's learning creative strategy
and he really wants to become one.
Um, and he loves just knowing like the ins and outs.
What would be your advice to Asim, like, as he's like trying
to level up, where,
what do you suggest he would he should do for like,
his advancement of his career besides being here?
Obviously,
Um, as, as I said, a a, a key component
for me was working closer with media buyers.
So I would say collaborating and, and, um, and,
and I mean like senior media buyers, you know, um, like,
like guys that have been in, in the reins of it
and, and question them.
You know, really question them.
Don't be afraid to ask dumb questions.
Um, and, and know that no idea is a bad idea.
Um, in order to be creative you gotta go through
a hundred s****y ideas to find the one good one.
So, um, you know, not, not
that like you gotta make a whole bunch of s**t
and then you'll find a good one.
But as in, in your mind, you go through a lot of ideas
until you eventually go, this is the best one.
Um, so always allow your brain to, to really flow, think
as creatively as you can.
But when it comes to going from video editor
to creative strategist, and, and it, and,
and this is interesting about the e-commerce space
because drawing the LAN of the roles
and responsibilities of a creative strategist
really can vary.
You know, when you think of cre like
as a creative strategist with a e-commerce brand, you know,
you could be creative with, with products,
you know, you with, with, um, designing the product,
with designing product ideas, with the packaging, with the,
you know, um, the branding.
Like that's all creative,
but that's not ad creative, you know?
Um, but it's still a creative strategist.
And, and creative can go from copywriting,
which is not visual.
It's text-based from copywriting to research to,
there's a lot of aspects of creative strategy
that isn't just a video ad or isn't just a graphic ad.
Um, there's a creative strategist revolves
a lot of other factors.
And you've gotta kind of piece together what you believe
to be the most important factors
and the factors that you love enough
that you'll study as deep as you can.
Um, and find out what those factors are.
And just set yourself out to be the person that's gonna go
and know the most about copyrighting more than anyone else
on this planet, if that's what you love.
Like find what you love about being a creative strategist
and make sure it's aligned with what
will make creative strategy better for e-commerce brands.
Um, and then go and do that, um,
and learn more about it
while you're doing what you're doing.
You can't drop what you're doing as a video editor
and go, I'm done being a video editor.
I'm gonna go be a creative strategist.
It's, you gotta do this while building until eventually,
you know, you can be at a point where you can take
that leap and you can extend.
So I would say keep doing
what you're doing, but keep building.
Don't just settle for video editor say,
the next goal I wanna go learn is copyrighting.
The next goal I want to go learn is,
you know, landing pages.
You know what, whatever it is, keep pushing yourself
to, to figure out more.
'cause e-commerce is all about funnels
and it's, there's, it's there,
there's a lot along the funnel from, from,
from getting a purchase, um, uh, off, off of an ad
that, that you gotta figure out.
So, yeah, but, but you gotta make sure you love it,
so you don't love it.
It's, you're not gonna be able to study it and, and,
and go really in depth into it, um,
without hating your life completely.
So, and no one wants to laugh at the head.
I love that. Yeah,
I would say that's the most important part.
Um, yeah, I think a,
a creative strategist evolves into one.
I don't think it, it, you just become one
because a creative strategist is like, encompasses all
aspects, can see from start to finish execution, ideation,
strategy, and, um, knows the most about the customer
and is be able to put that into tangible action.
Um, and honestly for me, like, so I,
I think I've told you guys, but yeah, I started off as a,
as a graphic designer, started off
as a landing page, uh, designer.
So I wasn't even into video before.
I didn't even know Photoshop. And it's like,
I worked at a direct response agency
and he taught me the principles
of persuasion, and I was like, what?
That's a thing. And then he was telling me
that every piece on a landing page has a significance to it.
There's a persuasive element to it.
You know, you, you, you're above the fold.
This is your headline. This is, you know,
this is your authority, this is your social.
And I was like, oh, now it's starting to make sense.
So the building blocks start there.
But then I was like, well, I've never,
I've never like ran ads before.
What's that like? You know?
And as you take on more of these responsibilities, you start
to see the bigger picture, right?
Because like before I was just like, oh,
I'm just a landing page guy.
Like, I love landing pages
and trying to make the coolest landing page ever.
But, um, you know, as you put more skills under your belt,
then, then that's when you'll be able to make, uh,
lead a team and make better decisions
as a strategist, in my opinion.
Um, start a drop shipping company
or like start, start just see what happens, you know,
it doesn't hurt like that teaches you the most is like,
do something and then fail at it.
Like, yeah, take the risk.
Um, the first, the first creative strategist roles I took,
I was not a good creative strategist.
I was not. Um, but you know, it's the learning that I
realized the mistake that I made on a brand
where I was like, dude, what a s**t video ad that was,
it could have been 10 times better.
Like I just learned, you can do hooks like this
and you can do this and your messaging can look like this
and you know, you can use emojis
and you can, you know, all of this.
And, um, as you make the mistakes
and learnings, you just get better and better and better.
You're not gonna, you're not gonna be the same creative
strategist after working five brands versus 50.
You, as you said, it's the evolution.
Um, and I'm still, I'm still growing
and still making mistakes, learning and,
and figuring things out.
Definitely. Yeah, no, I'm, I'm, I'm with you on that.
It's always, it's a challenge.
If it's not challenging, then you're not growing.
Um, I wanted to a Aaron, I wanted to hit you up
to see if you had any questions, brother.
Um, I think you're the only one I haven't addressed in the,
in the call today, if he's still there.
Uh, yeah, yeah. No, it was a great call for sure.
Um, I just had one question.
I guess, uh, maybe it's more about messaging than the
creative strategy, but do you guys have like metrics
that you look at to determine like lifetime value?
Like what, what creatives what videos
drove like a longer lifetime value rather than
just like first purchase?
Yeah, so yeah, meta gotta love meta.
Um, we, it's, it's obviously changed a lot.
Um, the, the metrics
and even the KPIs that we have set for
what is a good performing creative.
Um, but at the end of the day, we, we go to
Managers,
Sorry, I'm getting a internet
connection, unstable message.
Sounds like You're back. Am I back? Yeah. Am I back?
Sorry guys. Um,
and so we've gotta look at
where Facebook is putting most of the spend.
Um, first of all,
and usually that's a good telltale on what messaging
is resonating, not re resonating with
the customers the most or with the viewers.
Um, 'cause that's, that's how meta is, is judging where
to put the spin on which creative based off
of the interaction and the
engagement that those ads are getting.
So we flex is very different to a lot of brands, uh, uh, uh,
to a lot of agencies I've worked with Flex, we purely scale
ads based off of contribution,
contribution margin standpoint.
So the only metric we look at,
and that's how we scale our accounts.
And that's not good for ad creative.
That's the, i i I can't come here
and tell, uh, you know, creative people.
You've gotta look at the profitability of a brand and,
and scale creative according to profitability.
It's, it's, it's a's tough, tough thing to,
to tell creative people to do.
So from a metric point of view, we are looking at CPA, um,
and we want to make sure that the creatives below CPA,
'cause it doesn't matter how good the messaging is
or how good the drill
as is if we are not profitable on first time purchase.
And that's the gold majority of brands we work with.
If it's, you know, if we are paying too much
to acquire the customer, it's not a good creative
where we can't sustain growing the creative.
Um, and you can even look at things like cost per click,
you know, um, we, we've had some accounts where
every metric was good except cost per click
and it was unusually hard.
You know, it was like a crazy amount
that we're getting like cost per click.
And it's like, okay, cool.
From a creative strategy perspective
and a messaging standpoint, what do we gotta do
to just get cheaper clicks?
And, you know, we started running like meme ads
because it's like meme gets high engagement and,
and lots of comments and lots of shares
and um, that dramatically lowered cost per click
just, just by doing that.
And then by lowering it on some ad sets
and some campaigns, the overall ad accounts,
cost per click started lowering, which means we could start
spending a lot more, start scaling a lot more.
Um, I'm running around in circles,
but I think to answer your question directly, um,
we scale based for profit profitable metric,
we can look at hook rates,
we can look at click-through rates, we can look at,
you know, all those metrics that you base your creative off
of, but you can have a 80% click-through rate.
And if you're not getting purchases, you can't scale the ad.
So you've gotta look at it from a
conversion, um, standpoint.
Cool. Yeah, that helps a lot.
So like obviously as a brand owner,
you're looking at contribution margin.
What's the KPI that you set for the creative strategist?
Is it, are they looking at CPA then? Basically that's what,
So Yeah, yeah.
So in the core, current
Editors is a 50% success rate of creative batches, um, off
of new concept creative batches, not iteration batches.
Purely new concept, new angles, new messaging, um,
50% success rate as in success being above our,
the media buying KPR metrics
and the media buying metrics is
scaling based off target CPA.
Um,
hear me?
Uh, you cut out a little bit.
I think I got, I think I got you though.
Okay, cool. Sweet. Awesome. Thanks.
Thanks for asking Aaron.
Um, but yeah, rat is definitely eating your ethernet
cable. Um, yeah,
There was a huge storm today I think.
I think it was, it was that got some water in my,
in my cables probably.
So we got, uh, time
for two last questions, Ethan and Kale.
Um, I gotta head out after this,
but we'll just keep it under 10 minutes if we can.
Both of you. Ethan, if you wanna go first.
Yeah, sure. So I know you mentioned about memes being run
as ads and they seem to perform quite well.
I was wondered what your perspective was on.
So, you know, you have your four play boards,
which is like other ad uh, other people that are running ads
and good performing ones of them,
but you also take inspiration from
a lot of short form content.
You know, like things on TikTok where
like say one half is like GTA on the bottom
and the top half is like a podcast
and then the text in the middle.
Yeah. You know, things like that.
Do you, do you take inspiration from them for your ads
as they perform quite well
and are quite viral, like viral videos?
Yeah. Um, I wish I did more of it.
I do, so that my answer's yes,
but I actually wish I did it more
because I find so many brands get caught in this
basing their creative for their competitors,
which is the most dumbest thing.
It's like they see their competitors are running these ads
works, maybe it doesn't,
but the, I I don't think you should be basing your ad
creative strategy based off of competitors
and looking off of your competitors' ads.
I think a lot of creative strategies should be taken from
native platforms, native features, um,
TikTok, you know, all all those social media platforms
that people use on a frequent basis look at what is going
and why those native features are working.
But even native to the point of, I mean,
we busy making this ad, which, um, again,
I saw another brand ran,
which I thought was a crazy good idea,
but it's, you know, on, on our phone
where I'm just gonna open up a whole bunch of apps.
Um, and you have apps open up
and then when you swap up to close apps, it like,
it looks like that, I don't know if it's, uh,
the front app is the ad itself where it's got the product,
it's got the messaging that we want,
but the layouts of it is a layout that people are
so familiar with that it's a native feature
that they close the apps every day.
They're used to seeing this layout, like, let's make an ad
of something that they're so used to seeing.
And that's why things like TikTok comment, response,
you know, the, the TikTok comment response
graphic is often used in hooks
and those native features
where when you airdrop something people are making ads
where the videos inside of the airdrop, you know, design
and all these native features, it works
because you, it's familiarity when people see the ad,
they feel comfortable with it, they trust it, they like,
even if subconsciously they're seeing it
and they're like, I just trust it, just
because they're used to seeing it every day,
they might not realize like, oh, like I'm used
to seeing this every day,
but they just naturally feel that way.
So yeah, I would say any type of resource, nature,
features, styles, formats, music, sound,
whatever it is from other platforms, it does, you don't,
don't just take your
inspirational creative strategy from ads.
You want to, you wanna look outside of that.
Thank you very much.
Answered it perfectly. Oh my God, I'm
so excited you said that by the way.
I think, you know, I, I had forgotten about
that familiarity aspect, but it's so freaking true.
Like, it's, it's like everybody wants to buy,
I remember this line from my mentors, like, everybody wants
to buy, but not everybody, not everybody wants to be sold.
And so sometimes we're always as markers,
we're pushing the sale, right?
And, and some of these native things, these like, you know,
it's almost like less is more sometimes
and you know, it it, like you said,
somebody subconsciously already trusts something they're
familiar with and it's like you just,
you just slide into their dms, you know what I mean?
You're like, um,
but yeah, I I love pulling inspo from organic
because it's not biased by a marketer.
Yeah, exactly.
We, we tend to come in there and just like, ah,
like screw everything up.
Yeah. We got one last question
for kale and then, uh, we'll wrap it up.
Yes. Um, alright,
so my question is about actually organic content, uh,
for DTC brands specifically.
Um, and
because we are like going into 2024, we are, um,
we have some brands that we think like, uh,
is gonna be a big like needle mover to focus more on like,
uh, organic emails, like create more value, uh, for like
through like Instagram, email mar marketing,
but not like pushing sales, but actually giving value.
Um, and I just wanted to get your opinion on that
and if that's something that you work on
or like if you, at least if you don't do it, that, uh,
if you don't offer that service, if you,
you you like encourage them to, to, to, like
how do you work with organic besides, uh, the paid
and uh, like can you see significant changes in
how the ads perform
after implementing some organic content strategies?
Yeah, yeah.
Some of the best brands I've worked with performance is just
so good because they're organic.
Social media is so good, you know, when,
when you're running ads from the account
and they've got these true real organic followers
of, of tens of thousands, hundreds of thousands,
your ads are, are tailored towards that audience as well.
So the more your organic social media presence is developed,
the more your ad your ads can also be developed.
Um, or, or, or the targeting of your ads at least, um,
or at least the perceived audience that your ads go to is
that, that, that Facebook
uses at some points of its algorithm.
Um, and so yeah, we, we don't offer organic,
uh, social media for our clients
and we don't offer email yet.
Um, flex Labs just acquired a e-commerce, uh,
a email marketing agency.
Um, so we're gonna have an in-house email
marketing service that we're gonna offer.
'cause we do realize the importance of it.
But even when we have been working with brands
that don't do email, we, well, we, so flex
where I'm currently at is, is a bad example
'cause we work with established brands
and all the established brands we work
with already have email set up email.
SMS is kind of like a standard
for any established e-commerce brand.
And if they don't have that, then
they must be damn good at their creative strategy to get
to a point where they can be well established without it.
Um, 'cause email
and SMS is such a revenue driver for majority of,
or for every e-commerce brand.
Um, so before then we would have a list
of email SMS marketing agencies that we partner with
that we would recommend that they do use the services of.
Um, because it's, it's super crucial.
And, and what we, we've started to do is we've started
to consult brands on their organic social media.
So we don't, we don't take over their organic
social media, we don't run it.
Um, but we will consult with them
and we would say, Hey, here's a couple good
strategies that we're now working.
Hey, in your niche, this is working really well.
Here's some content ideas,
here's some creators in the space that can help.
Um, and we just give 'em good guidelines and guide them
and consult with them on it.
Um, but, but it's, it's not something that we offer.
But yes, tell your clients how valuable it is, tell them
that if they want to get to, you know, wherever
that they at, if they want to get to that next level,
that next stage of their business via revenue,
at some point they've gotta start implementing
good focus on organic social and email SMS.
It's a must. It is, it really is crucial.
Okay, perfect. Thanks for that answer.
But one, one, just one thing,
like when you say SMS like email,
I can understand you can send email like giving 10 tips,
10 tips, sorry about that.
10 tips for something, you know,
but through an SMSI, like do you do the same thing
through S-M-S-I-I-I don't quite,
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sorry.
Yeah. So e email SMS is kind of treated
as like the same, usually treated as the same service.
And it's usually, um, the same type
of strategy and approach.
You know, when you would send a, a email out
to your customer base saying, Hey,
we've got a new product that's launching.
They do the same thing just via to the SMS channel.
Um, they just send a SMS for it.
It's, it's a little bit more traditional marketing.
Um, but it's, I can, I can tell you what,
the more corporate brands that we work with, the brands
that have retail, um, spots
that are in retail have their own physical stores, um,
that are a little bit more than just the e-commerce brand,
um, that are a lot more corporate email, SMS, um,
is a lot more of a, of a thing.
Amazing. Thank much For that.
All right, team, thank you so much, James
for sharing your wisdom today.
Um, that was like, thank you guys, incredibly enjoyed it.
Valuable call. Thank you so much for sharing
and I got a ton for myself
and it's amazing to see, uh,
a fellow creative here in the space with, with
as much experience as you.
Um, thank you guys for joining the call
and we'll have a new guest for next week
and I'm looking forward to seeing you guys there.
Thank you very much. Thanks for
the great questions guys. All.
Cheers everybody. Bye. Thanks. Cheers.